[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Extempore means:",
    "options": ["impromptu", "planned", "improvise", "immediate"],
    "answer": "impromptu"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "\"Antonym: \"\"Menacing\"\"__\"",
    "options": ["encouraging", "promising", "auspicious", "alarming"],
    "answer": "auspicious"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Antonym of \"Oblige\"",
    "options": ["Require", "Bind", "Censure", "Bother"],
    "answer": "Censure"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Antonym of Cynical",
    "options": ["Liberal", "Pessimistic", "Gullible", "Equivocal"],
    "answer": "Liberal"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "\"\"\"We were no more surprised than Rahman.\"\"",
    "options": [
      "We were all surprised",
      "We were less surprise than Rahman",
      "Rahman was less surprised than us",
      "We were as surprised as Rahman."
    ],
    "answer": "We were less surprise than Rahman"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "\"\"\"Not once has neighbour invited us into his house.\"\"",
    "options": [
      "Our neighbour has never invite us into his house",
      "Our neighbour has invited us in his house not once but many times",
      "Occasionally our neighbour has invited us into his house.",
      "Our neighbour has not always invited us into his house"
    ],
    "answer": "Our neighbour has invited us in his house not once but many times"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Travellers____their reservation well in advance if they want to visit the St. Martins island.",
    "options": [
      "had better to to get",
      "had better get",
      "had to better get",
      "had better got"
    ],
    "answer": "had better get"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "After food has been dried or canned ___ for later consumption.",
    "options": [
      "it should be stored",
      "that it should be stored",
      "should be stored",
      "which should be stored"
    ],
    "answer": "it should be stored"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Despite being a brilliant scientist, he does not seem to get his ideas across.",
    "options": [
      "get his ideas down part",
      "make his ideas understood",
      "summarise his ideas",
      "put together his ideas"
    ],
    "answer": "make his ideas understood"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What may be considered courteous in one culture may be arrogant in another.",
    "options": ["gracious", "coarse", "flimsy", "friendly"],
    "answer": "gracious"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which of the word or words are wrong. Every man or women should vote their vote.",
    "options": ["should vote", "for", "their", "Every"],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which word or words are incorrect? A doctor may be able to diagnose a problem perfect but he may not be able to find a drug to which the patient will respond.",
    "options": ["will respond", "which", "diagnose", "perfect"],
    "answer": "perfect"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which word or words are incorrect? According to experts a good way to improve listening skills is by watch television specially news and documentaries.",
    "options": ["by", "watch", "improve", "to"],
    "answer": "watch"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Choose the pair of words that expresses a relationship similar to that of the given pair-- WORDS:WRITER",
    "options": [
      "Laws:Policeman",
      "Brick :Bricklayer",
      "Chalk: black board",
      "Joy:emotion"
    ],
    "answer": "Brick :Bricklayer"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Choose the pair of words that expresses a relationship similar to that of the given pair-- PATRON:SUPPORT",
    "options": [
      "Artist:imitation",
      "Spouce:divorce",
      "Counselor:advice",
      "Restaurant:customer"
    ],
    "answer": "Counselor:advice"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Choose the pair of words that expresses a relationship similar to that of the given pair--- HEART:HUMAN",
    "options": ["Wall:brick", "Hand:child", "Kitchen:house", "Engine: car"],
    "answer": "Engine: car"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "\"\"\"No news is good news\"\"\"",
    "options": [
      "it is likely to have bad news",
      "It is likely that we expect bad news",
      "it is likely that nothing bad has happend",
      "it is unlikely that nothing bad has happend"
    ],
    "answer": "It is likely that we expect bad news"
  },

  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "A bird in hand is worth two in the bush.",
    "options": [
      "The seen is better than the unseen",
      "Take what you have readily available rather than expecting better in the future",
      "Promises are better than actuals",
      "It is no good beating about the bush."
    ],
    "answer": "Take what you have readily available rather than expecting better in the future"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "The sentence : Who would have thought Shylock was so unkind \" express_\"",
    "options": ["hyperbole", "interrogation", "command", "wonder"],
    "answer": "wonder"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "To 'raise ones brows' indicate_",
    "options": ["surprise", "annoyance", "disapproval", "indifference"],
    "answer": "surprise"
  }
]
